Nagizaka Kouji Enchou Chu!
I'm Sayato Kanagawa, and I'm Nao Tomisato.
And Nagizaka-chan!
How are you?
Please choose me!
Please announce today's plan!
Nagizaka's own audition!
Enchou Chu!
So, in Enchou Chu,
all the members of Nagizaka
will choose a person
who fits the theme
and see the relationship
of the members.
So, the first question is...
Muzinto Survival Challenge!
Rio chose this one!
The 5 people I chose are...
Ta-da! They look like this.
Ozu-chan, Kaki-san, Mitsuki, Ichinose-san,
and me.
I'm curious about the picture on the side.
The picture on the side is a hint.
Ozu-chan is very smart, and she can also
exercise.
She has a lot of physical abilities, so of
course she can choose a girlfriend.
Kaki-san said she likes professional
models.
So I thought she must be good at building
a ship or a boat, so I chose Taki-san.
And Setoguchi was chosen in the main story
as well, right?
I think she was chosen for that reason,
but I think she has a lot of upper biceps
muscles.
Her arms are really tight.
I'm sure they'll carry heavy materials
with them.
That's right, they'll carry them with
energy.
I'm sure they'll carry heavy materials
with them.
Miku, you're good at sumo, aren't you?
I'm the strongest in sumo.
If a beast comes out,
I want you to do your best.
That's a good thing.
That's right.
The last one is me.
I'm the first character to die.
You said it.
That's right.
If a monster comes out, I'll be the first
to die.
I'm the type to sacrifice myself.
I can determine if I can eat food or if I
can eat this.
Please leave it to us.
She's saying it from her heart.
But surprisingly, there is a possibility
that this is the correct answer.
Really?
Isn't it?
That's right.
I feel like Ozu-chan and Mitsuki-chan are
in it every time.
That's true.
Mitsuki-chan seems to be able to do
anything.
She seems to be able to do anything.
That's true.
Then, the next person to choose is...
Nao!
Yes!
I also chose.
Ta-da!
Ozu-chan, Ogawa Yumikki-san, Okuda
Tomisato-san
They all look like they have a lot of
knowledge
Eh? Why?
They all look like they have a lot of
knowledge
Eh? They all look like they have a lot of
They all look like they have a lot of
knowledge
Do you think Aya will do it?
Do you think she will do it?
Maybe she won't do it?
Do you have an image of Ogawa?
No, I don't.
She can't climb up the tree.
What can she do if she climbs up the tree?
There is a possibility that she can only
climb up the tree.
I have an image that she can pick up the
food on the tree.
I can't pick it up.
I wonder if I can pick it up.
Even though the tree is so small.
I can't deny that.
It's okay. There are still more.
That's right.
Next is Yumeki-san.
Yumeki-san will go to the sea and catch
fish.
I understand.
And Iroha will bring something she doesn't
need.
But I think it will be cute and healing.
But I don't need it.
I was worried about it.
I praise her.
Yes
How many years have you been doing this?
I feel like she's going to heal me
She's cute
I have to put myself in it
I'm looking at them
Don't you do anything?
I don't do anything
You don't do anything?
Well...
I don't want to do anything
I'm going to make her work
I'm looking at everyone's movements
Even if you come to my house, I'm just
looking at you
No, wait, that's not it
I'm just making fun of you
No, it's not like that.
But didn't we have a dinner party the
other day?
We had a dinner party.
I had been grilling meat for two hours.
Oh, I see.
Oh, Renia-san!
Wasn't it the same team?
It wasn't the same team.
I'm sorry, it wasn't the same team.
I'm sorry.
It was the same team.
Every time we had dinner together, she
said,
But I had been grilling meat for two hours
at the dinner party.
That's all she said.
She said that all the time.
I don't want to say it.
Why is it like this?
I don't know why.
Let's move on to the next topic.
Please.
Ideal family selection.
So, who will answer this topic?
SAKUTA.
Yes.
This one.
It looks calm.
Mom is Okuda Iroha.
Dad is Kaki Haruka.
My older sister is me, my younger sister
is Nao, and my pet is Aya Ogawa.
It's a family that seems to have a slow
flow of time.
Iroha is good at cooking, and I often stay
with her, but she has a very calm
personality, so I thought that a child
would grow up to be a kind child, so I
became a mother.
I want Iroha to raise me.
I don't know.
So I chose Iroha.
My father is Kaki-san.
I want to play catch ball with Kaki-san on
holidays.
I can't imagine it.
That's true.
She seems to be good at it.
It's just her image.
And my older sister is me.
Why?
Because she is my older sister,
I thought it would be me if we were
siblings.
That's true.
But if I don't need her, I'll choose Saya-
san.
I was drawing it at first, but I don't
have a place to put it anymore.
I'm happy.
Well, but it's not in it.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm strong today, so I'm a
little calm.
Please calm down.
But I made my sister Nao.
Yay!
Because you pamper me.
I often do it to Hina.
No, but in this calm family, I'm a
little...
Why?
I'm quite calm.
It's terrible.
I can feel the wind.
I'm sorry.
Thank you, Sakuta.
My pet is Aya Ogawa.
I see.
Aya's skin is like a baby's.
Her skin is like a baby's.
It's similar to Ayame's.
Her skin is a little hard.
I wanted to touch her as a pet.
That's why I chose her.
Isn't Aya a pet or a little sister?
I feel like it's going to be one of them.
Next, I chose the family composition.
I'm looking forward to it.
Ta-da!
Mom, Tsutsui.
Father, Kaki.
Sister, Tamura.
Little sister, Kawasaki.
Pet, Misato.
Huh?
Are they both pets?
Because they both have a pet, they might
become pets.
I'm sure they want to go up.
Shut up!
It's scary. I can't continue.
But Saku-tan was my little sister.
I'm glad.
When I realized, she was my little sister.
When I joined, Mayu-tan kept calling me
Onee-chan, Onee-chan.
I don't have an older sister, so I used to
call my sister the name of the message.
She's so cute.
She's like an older sister.
And my father is...
I can understand.
He's so clear-headed.
That's true.
I thought he was the best.
He's firm.
And my mother is Tsutsuya.
She has a strong desire to grow up in a
peaceful family.
But I don't think I'm part of it.
I thought so, too.
Saya is the same as Aruna.
I didn't watch it.
You can't do that, really.
Then, if you were to choose, who would it
be?
I think it would be my older sister.
Oh, I see.
After all, there are four sisters who are
the oldest.
I understand.
Because she's your pet.
No, no, no.
Because she's your sister.
I understand how you felt when you said
you didn't like Saya-chan earlier.
You don't understand? Why would I?
Okay, so let's move on to the next topic.
Okay.
If you were to open a store, what would
you choose?
Okay.
This one.
Riria-san.
Ta-da!
These five people!
The pictures look so good!
Don't you think the balance is really
good?
It was in the main story, but Tere-chan
has the best sense of art in Nogizaka,
so I want her to do the interior and the
design beautifully.
She seems to be able to make the world
view properly, so I chose her.
Next is Ozu-chan.
Ozu-chan is quite popular.
After all, it's brain.
Because it's Nagizaka's brain.
Ozu-chan.
After all, it's not about accounting or
money.
I want to ask a smart girl to calculate.
I want to ask Ozu-chan.
Next is Nao-chan.
I thought it was a restaurant, so I
thought about the store.
I like people who can cook, so I have an
image of Nao-chan who can cook in
Nogizaka.
She is a member of a large family, so even
if she is busy, she seems to be able to be
put together.
I want you to be a chef.
What are those bug glasses on the side?
No, it's a frying pan.
I'm sorry.
Good.
You are a senior.
I'm sorry.
Next, Koko-chan is the type of person who
loves everyone even when she's in a mess
in the hall.
She's the type of person who loves
everyone even when she's in a mess in the
hall.
She's the type of person who loves
everyone even when she's in a mess in the
hall.
She's the type of person who loves
everyone even when she's in a mess in the
hall.
She's the type of person who loves
everyone even when she's in a mess in the
hall.
She's the type of person who loves
everyone even when she's in a mess in the
hall.
She's the type of person who loves
everyone even when she's in a mess in the
hall.
She's the type of person who loves
everyone even when she's in a mess in the
hall.
She's the type of person who loves
everyone even when she's in a mess in the
hall.
Yes, she has a lot of charm, so I want her
to be in charge of the hall.
That's a good idea.
The atmosphere of the store is going to be
very bright.
That's true.
I think it's good.
Lastly, I was wondering what to do, but I
want her to be the owner.
Actually, I've been a class president for
a long time, and when I was in elementary
school, I was also the student council
president, so I want to be in charge of
organizing it.
I want to go to the student council
president's school.
I really want to go.
By the way, what do you think it is?
What do you think it is?
It's like a cafe restaurant.
I think it's a little fashionable.
I'll show you here.
Thank you very much.
And the next one is Hina.
Yes.
I'm here.
I'm Iroha Fukuda.
I'm Nao Kimiki.
I'm Sakura Endo.
I'm Mao Hiyoki.
I'm Nagi Inoue.
Oh, I see.
I didn't listen to the story.
You didn't listen to the story?
You mean your name?
Who is this person?
I don't think so.
What are you guys talking about?
I'm watching the show.
It's okay. Let's make a new wind.
By the way, let's start with Iroha.
Can I?
Iroha is a good cook.
She is a good cook.
Yumeki is good at cooking.
She is really good.
I personally went to a Japanese sweets
shop.
Oh, that's really nice.
I brought some dumplings.
And Mao went to a sushi shop.
Oh, sushi!
Like the ones that are wrapped like this?
It's different.
It's different?
That's right!
I see.
I brought some fish.
And Nagi brought some o-hagi.
Oh, o-hagi.
Yes, I brought some o-hagi.
O-hagi?
Nagi's o-hagi.
Everything was different, wasn't it?
Well, everything was different, but I
think it's good.
Then, if Hina manages her own business,
what kind of store would you like?
I want to open an eyelash salon.
Don't be so realistic.
I thought it would be something like that,
but it's about eyelashes.
I want to raise the eyelashes of a girl
and make her happy.
I want to make a girl happy.
Let's move on to the next topic.
The next topic is...
Mugi-zaka version of Cinderella.
This is Luna.
I am...
Cinderella is Yuna Shibata.
I am the magician.
The mean mother is Mayu Tamura.
The mean daughter is Nao Yumeki.
The prince is Kaki.
There are four of them.
For Yuna-chan, Aruno was mentioned in the
main story, but I really think she looks
good as a heroine, so it came to my mind
at first.
And I think her relationship is also good.
I see.
And for the two who are mean, they often
play a play.
They seem to have the most fun.
The two of them. I can imagine them.
For the Magician, I had to put myself in
it, so I put myself in it.
If I didn't put myself in it, I wanted to
put Haruka Kuromi in it.
It's the most magical face, isn't it?
That's why I chose it.
By the way, did you know that Yuna likes
Cinderella?
I didn't know. I didn't know it at all,
but I thought it looked like it, so I put
it in.
Thank you. Let's move on to the next
topic.
Next is the selection that will make you
excited even if you do karaoke.
Did you do this before?
I haven't done it yet.
First of all, from Lillia, please.
This member, ta-da!
Here it is!
It looks fun, doesn't it?
I want to try it, but first of all, Mayu-
tan is honest, she will cheer me up no
matter where I am.
Not only in karaoke.
My image is that Mayu-tan will support me.
Even if I sing a song that no one knows or
is not famous,
Mayu-tan will praise me like, that song is
good, I want to listen to it before.
That kind of existence is important.
That's why I chose Mayu-tan.
RENTA-chan, to be honest, I've done all-
out karaoke with Sanky before.
That's nice.
RENKA-chan is the type of person who gets
up pretty early in the morning, so even if
she does all-out karaoke, her tension
doesn't change.
She doesn't get sleepy or feel down, and
she keeps talking to me, so I'm grateful
for that.
That's nice.
RENKA-san, that's nice.
Nagi-chan will be able to listen to it
first, so she will be able to order it and
ask what she wants to drink or what she
wants to eat, and I really like Anisong,
so I want to listen to Nagi-chan's Anisong
and go crazy.
It sounds fun.
If you ask me what song I want to sing, I
think I can sing it right away.
That's why I want to make a request.
I want to hear it.
Next, Aru-chan.
When the tension rises in the middle of
the night,
I want to listen to Aru-chan's singing
ballad and cry.
Cry.
I heard it in the middle of the night.
I want to cry a little.
Personally, I think karaoke is a wide
range of genres that I know, so I think I
can understand it even if someone sings a
minor song, so I think I can liven it up a
little.
I think so.
I think so too.
I think we can do it.
I want you to go somewhere.
I want to see it.
Please let us see it.
Next, Rio chose this.
Here it is.
Ta-da.
There are five of us.
If I were to say my wish, I would like her
to repeat the shout of ACTUALLY over and
over again.
Anyway, I want to enjoy the shout of
ACTUALLY.
Your throat is going to break.
I want her to shout the shout of ACTUALLY.
Iroha-san, I want you to sing the song of
Disney Princess like Ariel.
Gon-chan is good at anything, so it's
similar to Maeta-san's reason.
No matter what song she sings, she seems
to be good at anything.
Yumeki-san is also similar to Gon-chan,
and seems to be good at anything.
Do you know the poem of Hakata?
What?
The poem of Hakata?
I want Yumeki-san to sing karaoke at the
end of the song.
I want Yumeki-san to sing at the end of
the song.
I wanted to hear Yuuki-san's Hakata
poetry, so I chose you.
That's true.
I like to play maracas, so I can play
maracas.
I want to wear sunglasses and sing Taylor
Swift.
I want to go with Rio-chan.
Sounds fun.
I can speak English.
I want to sing.
It's so cool to sing in English.
I want to sing in English.
It's really a song, isn't it?
Why are you asking for a lesson?
It's fine, you can do it by yourself.
That's all for today.
How was it, everyone?
It was so quick.
It was good.
It was fun because it was related to
everyone.
I understand the rules, but I want to do
it again in the store.
No, understand it from the beginning.
Please do it alone.
Let me listen to it again.
Well then, today we have Riria-san, who
likes all-karaoke.
Can I have you close your eyes for the
last time?
Let's go until morning!